parishilton.com 2011-05-25

# ParisHilton.com Online Privacy Policy - Paris Hilton

Welcome to www.parishilton.com (the “ **Website** ”), a wholly owned business unit of Paris Hilton Entertainment, Inc., a California corporation (“ **Paris Hilton Entertainment** ”, “ **we** ”, “ **us** ” or “ **our** ”), hosted by our third-party service provider, Six Apart Ltd. (“ **Six Apart** ”), on a software platform owned and controlled by Six Apart. We respect your privacy and the security of your personal information, and recognize the importance of providing a secure environment for those who visit our Website and use our products and online tools. We have adopted this online Privacy Policy (this “ **Privacy Policy** ”) that guides how we collect, store, use and protect the information you provide us. This Privacy Policy details how we safeguard the privacy of our on-line visitors. PLEASE READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY CAREFULLY. 

By using this Website, you signify your assent to this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not use this Website. This Privacy Policy may change from time to time, so please check back periodically to ensure that you are aware of any changes. If we make a material change to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you by posting the change on this Website or in this Privacy Policy and, if necessary, give you additional choices regarding such change. Your continued use of our Website will signify your acceptance of these changes. 

**Please keep in mind that this Privacy Policy does not apply to, and cannot control, the activities on any other sites other than the Website. In addition, we are not responsible for the privacy of any information that you reveal or post in any public forum on the Website or which you reveal to any user of the Website (on community message boards, in blogs, on public profile pages, etc.). Information, including personally identifiable information, you submit via the Website will also be collected by Six Apart. For information on Six Apart’s use and disclosure of such information, please visit[Six Apart’s Privacy Policy](http://www.typepad.com/legal/privacy-policy.html). We are not responsible for Six Apart’s use, collection, or disclosure of your information, or Six Apart’s compliance with its privacy policy.**

This Privacy Policy will tell you: 

  * What personal and non-personal information does Paris Hilton Entertainment collect?
  * Who is collecting your information? 
  * How will Paris Hilton Entertainment use your personally identifiable information? 
  * With whom may Paris Hilton Entertainment share your personally identifiable information? 
  * What are your choices regarding the collection, use, and distribution of your personally identifiable information? 
  * Does Paris Hilton Entertainment collect information from children? 
  * What are cookies and how does Paris Hilton Entertainment use them? 
  * What are pixel tags and how does Paris Hilton Entertainment use them?
  * What are Internet protocol addresses? 
  * How secure is your personally identifiable information? 
  * What should you do if you want to correct or review your personally identifiable information, or have any questions or complaints?

**What personal and non-personal information does Paris Hilton Entertainment collect?**

Paris Hilton Entertainment collects two types of information: personally identifiable information and non-personally identifiable information. 

_Personally Identifiable Information_. Personally identifiable information is information that can be used to identify you or contact you. Paris Hilton Entertainment only collects personally identifiable information on a voluntary basis. Personally identifiable information collected may include your name, photographs, home address, phone number, date of birth, e-mail address, and/or billing information. We do not require this information to gain access to our Website; however, you will not be able to utilize certain features that require registration or receive materials such as newsletters unless such information is provided. Unless you give us permission to do so, we will not sell, share, license, trade, or rent your personally identifiable information other than as set forth in this Privacy Policy.

_Non-Personally Identifiable Information_. For some activities, we may ask you to create a username and password and/or to provide other, non-personal information such as your age, gender, or education level, and we may combine such information with your personally identifiable information. In addition, your web browser or client software may transmit certain geographic information or information regarding your computer (capabilities, browser, IP addresses, etc.) to us. We may use this information to help us understand who uses our Website and to improve and market our Website in general and to help us to improve the products and tools we offer online. In addition, we may use such information for security, system integrity (the prevention of hacking, etc.), or enforcement purposes. Because your non-personally identifiable information does not identify you, we reserve the right to share such information with our affiliates and other third parties for any purpose. 

**Who is collecting your information?**

When you are asked for information while on the Website, you are sharing that information with Paris Hilton Entertainment and its various affiliates, and Six Apart, unless specifically stated otherwise. As a result of this sharing, you may receive communications from any of Paris Hilton Entertainment or its affiliates, or as provided in [Six Apart’s Privacy Policy](http://www.typepad.com/legal/privacy-policy.html). In addition, some services are provided in conjunction with partner companies. If your personally identifiable information is being collected by a company other than Paris Hilton Entertainment, its affiliates, and/or Six Apart, you will be notified at the time the information is collected. If you do not want your information shared, you can choose not to allow the transfer of information by not using that particular service or by not providing any information at that time. 

Please be aware that we cannot control the activities of third parties to whom we provide data, and as such we cannot guarantee that they adhere to the same privacy and security procedures as we do. 

Please be aware that advertisers or websites with links to our Website may collect personally identifiable information about you. And remember, this Privacy Policy does not apply to, and cannot control the activities of, those other advertisers or websites. 

**How will Paris Hilton Entertainment use your personally identifiable information?**

The personally identifiable information you provide to us will allow us to personalize your online experience; to communicate with you; to allow other users to contact you; fulfill your purchases; alert you to new products or services, features, or enhancements; and/or notify you of contests, promotions, or special events and offers. We may enhance or merge the personally identifiable information collected through our Website with non-personally identifiable information or data from third parties. 

Through our referral tools for informing a friend about our Website, we will automatically send your friend a one-time email containing the information you request to be sent. If you elect to use these referral tools, we will collect from you certain personally identifiable information about your friend which you have provided, such as your friend's name and email address. We do not store your friend’s information or use it for any other purpose.

Lastly, we may use your personally identifiable information for internal marketing, profiling, or demographic purposes, so we can adapt our products and services to better suit your needs. We do this to better understand and serve our users. 

Please be advised that this Privacy Policy does not protect you when you use our public forums or provide information (including personally identifiable information) about yourself through the public profile feature or through any community area available on the Website, even if said information is marked “private”. You should carefully consider any information you disclose in any public forum, or to any other user, or through the public profile feature, on our Website. 

**With whom may Paris Hilton Entertainment share your personally identifiable information?**

We may need to disclose your personally identifiable information to third party vendors to fulfill product orders or prizes, to process mailings, or to process, analyze, and/or store data. We will attempt to ensure that these entities do not use your personally identifiable information for any other purpose, and that they have agreed to maintain the confidentiality, security, and integrity of the personally identifiable information they obtain from us.

If you affirmatively opt-in allow us to share your personally identifiable information with third parties for their marketing purposes, Paris Hilton Entertainment may share your personally identifiable information with such third parties to allow them to contact you regarding products, programs, services and/or promotions that may be of interest to you. To opt-out of receiving marketing materials or messages from third parties with whom we have shared your personally identifiable information hereunder, please utilize the opt-out mechanisms set forth in such third parties’ marketing materials and/or privacy policy. 

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law or in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing such information is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against you if you are violating the terms of service or use agreements for our Website or product, or may be causing injury to or interference (intentionally or unintentionally) with our rights or property, other users of our Website or products, or anyone else who could be harmed by your activities. 

As with any business, your personally identifiable information is also an asset of Paris Hilton Entertainment and will become part of our normal business records. As such, we may also disclose your personally identifiable information to a third party if we decide to sell a line of business to that third party, so you can continue to receive service and information in connection with that line of business with as little disruption as possible. Similarly, in the event of a merger, acquisition, reorganization, bankruptcy, or other similar event, your personally identifiable information may be transferred to our successor or assign. 

Our Website also contains message boards, chat areas and blogs, where users can exchange ideas and communicate with one another. When posting to a message board, chat area or blog, please be aware that the information is being made publicly available on-line and the user does so at user’s own risk. WE ARE NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR THE USE OR DISCLOSURE OF ANY INFORMATION YOU VOLUNTARILY DISCLOSE THROUGH OUR WEBSITE. 

**What are your choices regarding the collection, use, and distribution of your personally identifiable information?**

We allow you to control the way that we use personally identifiable information that we might obtain. At the time you provide personally identifiable information, we may give you the option of declining any future offers or information about new products, promotions, or services. In addition, many of the “mailings” we may send you, such as newsletters, have procedures within them to cancel the receipt of any future mailings. You may modify any of your personally identifiable information or change your account settings at any time by logging into your account and using the edit profile feature. 

**Does Paris Hilton Entertainment collect information from children?**

We are committed to the privacy of children, and our Website and online tools and products are not designed for or directed to children under 13 years of age. Once a child states that his/her age is under 13, we do not collect or store any personally identifiable information such as name, address, or email address. We urge parents or guardians to participate in their children’s exploration of the Internet, and to instruct their children to never give out their real names, addresses, phone numbers, or other information without permission, when on-line.

**What are cookies and how does Paris Hilton Entertainment use them?**

Cookies are a feature of your Web browser that allows websites to transfer bits of information to your computer for record-keeping purposes. A cookie stored on your computer can be used to “remember” things like your password, or that you have already registered. This allows us to speed up your future activities, saving the time you would normally spend entering information such as your password or registration. In addition, we may use cookies to retrieve user information for promotional, marketing, or security purposes. 

We also may use cookies to conduct marketing and promotional efforts, tailor certain advertisements to your browser that we think may be of interest to you, or to determine the popularity of certain content. We may link the information stored in cookies to personally identifiable information you provide us, and to personalize your Website experience we may store personally identifiable information you provide us in an encrypted form in temporary or “session” cookies, which are erased when you close your browser. 

In addition to cookies that we place on your computer, cookies may also be placed on your computer by third parties that we use to display or serve advertisements or to collect non-personally identifiable information in order to provide advertising-related services. For example, in the course of serving advertisements, our third-party ad servers may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser.

You do not have to accept cookies to use our Website; however, you may not be able to use certain products, offerings, features, or resources of our Website if you do not accept cookies. Although most browsers are initially set to accept cookies, you may reset your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie or to reject cookies generally. Most browsers offer instructions on how to do so in the "Help" section of the toolbar.

**What are Pixel Tags and how does Paris Hilton Entertainment use them?**

We and/or our third party service providers may use “pixel tags,” “web beacons,” “clear GIFs” or similar mechanisms (collectively, “ **Pixel Tags** ”) in connection with the Website to compile statistics about usage of the Website, to determine response rates, to determine the effectiveness of promotional efforts, and for other purposes. 

**What are Internet protocol addresses?**

An Internet Protocol (“ **IP** ”) address is the unique number assigned to your server or Internet Service Provider. We may track such IP addresses for system administration, to report aggregate information, site tracking, security purposes, or to prevent our servers from being abused. 

**How secure is your personally identifiable information?**

We have taken steps to put in place industry-standard measures to assure that all information collected will remain secure and in its original form (i.e., free from any alteration) and we make good-faith efforts to store your personally identifiable information in a secure operating environment. In addition, we will take reasonable steps to assure that third parties to whom we transfer any data will provide sufficient protection of personally identifiable information. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be absolutely secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personally identifiable information, we cannot ensure the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk.

**What should you do if you want to correct or review your personally identifiable information, or have any questions or complaints?**

If for any reason you have any questions, are concerned with the way we are using your personally identifiable information, or would like to correct or request that we delete such personally identifiable information, please contact us by e-mailing us at [contact@parishilton.com](mailto:contact@parishilton.com).

**This Privacy Policy was last updated on January 14, 2010.**

Paris Hilton Entertainment  
2934 1/2 Beverly Glen Circle, Suite 383  
Bel Air, CA 90077
